It looks like snow!
Wow!
This is the end for the cherry blossoms this year then.
We don't have school tomorrow, so let's watch flowers together!
That sounds like fun! Should I make lunchboxes?
I'll cook too!
Come on now...
That's great!
Hurray!
Listen to me...
Sorry for agreeing without asking you...
No, no... It's perfectly fine with me.
I'll try to make something too.
Thank you.
Kouki's always causing you so much trouble...
Well... You don't need to worry about that.
Kouki! Rin!
Let's meet tomorrow morning at eight in the park, okay?
Okie!
That's too early...
Then nine!
People don't watch flowers that early in the morning.
Then how about ten...
Oh wait, I gotta watch Gransazer!
Then let's make it noon, shall we?
Daikichi!
Daikichi, where are the bottles?
Aren't they under the sink?
Oh, right.
It might rain tomorrow.
There's a spring storm coming in.
Storm...
It's already raining!
Oh man! And quite hard too.
Let's make good-weather charms!
Daikichi!
The rain stopped!
That's lucky.
Our charms saved the day!
Seems the wind might've stripped the trees...
It smells like green!
All the flowers are gone!
Hey there!
Kouki!
Daikichi!
The sky is blooming!
The Sky is Blooming